<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>RE-Dojo</title>
    <link>https://re-dojo.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on RE-Dojo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 15:54:02 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://re-dojo.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>[NSEC 2018] Mars Analytica (20)</title>
      <link>https://re-dojo.github.io/post/2018-10-28-mars-analytica/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Oct 2018 13:37:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://re-dojo.github.io/post/2018-10-28-mars-analytica/</guid>
      <description>In May 2018, the NorthSec conference and its on-site CTF competition were held. Once again the competition was awesome, the challenges were very diverse and the infrastructure was well configured. One of the reverse engineering challenges was a program called MarsAnalytica. This challenge remained unsolved at the end of the CTF. This binary was worth a lot of points and I think it was the right amount of points due to the time one would have to spend to solve it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[ECW 2017] Red Diamond (175)</title>
      <link>https://re-dojo.github.io/post/2018-09-28-ecw-binary3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 13:37:00 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://re-dojo.github.io/post/2018-09-28-ecw-binary3/</guid>
      <description>Pour la deuxième année consécutive, Thales et Airbus ont organisé un CTF à destination des étudiants européens: le challenge ECW. Tout comme l&amp;rsquo;année dernière, celui-ci est séparé en une épreuve qualificative individuelle (CTF Jeopardy classique) et une phase finale par équipe avec un format Attaque/Défense.
L&amp;rsquo;épreuve qualificative de cette année reprenait les catégories classiques de CTF: Web, Forensics, Crypto et Reverse.
Parmis les 4 challenges de reverse qui étaient proposés, voici la solution de celui qui m&amp;rsquo;a paru le plus intéressant mais également le plus compliqué à résoudre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About the dojo</title>
      <link>https://re-dojo.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://re-dojo.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our reverse engineering dojo!
Here you will find different articles about reverse engineering, binary analysis and logical programming, mostly related to CTF challenges.
Blog posts are either written in french or english depending on our mood.
Thanks for reading!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dojo contact</title>
      <link>https://re-dojo.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://re-dojo.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description> First Name  Last Name  E-Mail  City  State AL CA IL      Send   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>